Guide to the Levy Dime Novel Collection 1821-1968 Levy
© 2012 Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series I: Novels (Box 1-83)
  - Author: Dale, Alan Title: An eerie he and she City: New York Publisher: G. W. Dillingham Date: 1889 (Box 21, Folder 416)
  - Author: Dale, Darley Title: Reuben Foreman, the village blacksmith Series Title: The Choice Series Series Number: 72 City: New York Publisher: Robert Bonner's Sons Date: 1892 (Box 21, Folder 417)
  - Author: Dale, Mrs. Title: Behind the silver veil Series Title: Lovell's Library Series Number: 1274 City: New York Publisher: John W. Lovell Date: 1888 (Box 21, Folder 418)
  - Author: Dallas, Mary Kyle Title: The cuban heiress City: New York Publisher: F. M. Lupton Format: hard cover Date: 1892 (Box 21, Folder 419)
  - Author: Dallas, Mary Kyle Title: The cuban heiress Series Title: The Bijou Series Series Number: 61 City: New York Publisher: F. M. Lupton Date: 1892 (Box 21, Folder 420)
  - Author: Dallas, Mary Kyle Title: Eunice Earle; or, the fatal compact Series Title: The Arm Chair Library Series Number: 103 City: New York Publisher: F. M. Lupton Date: undated (Box 21, Folder 421)
  - Author: Dallas, Mary Kyle Title: Grace Garrick; or, true love and false Series Title: The Arm Chair Library Series Number: 114 City: New York Publisher: F. M. Lupton Date: undated (Box 21, Folder 422)
  - Author: Danby, Frank Title: The copper crash Series Title: Seaside Library Series Number: 1379 City: New York Publisher: George Munro Date: 1890 (Box 21, Folder 423)
  - Author: D'Annunzio, Gabriele Title: The triumph of death Series Title: The Ivy Series Series Number: 107 City: New York Publisher: George Munro's Sons Date: 1900 (Box 21, Folder 424)
  - Author: Daudet, Alphonse Title: The partners or Fromont, Jr., and Risler, Sr. Series Title: Arrow Library Series Number: 67 City: New York Publisher: Street and Smith Date: 1893 (Box 21, Folder 425)
  - Author: Davis, Caroline E. Kelly, Mrs. Title: The squire's daughter City: Boston Publisher: Henry Hoyt Format: hard cover Date: 1869 (Box 21, Folder 426)
  - Author: Dean, Edwin S. Title: Was she his wife? Series Title: Leisure-Time Series Series Number: 17 City: New York Publisher: W. D. Rowland Date: 1892 (Box 21, Folder 427)
  - Author: De La Ramee ("Ouida") Title: Friendship, a story of society Series Title: Crown Series Series Number: 100 City: New York Publisher: George Munro's Sons Date: 1898 (Box 21, Folder 428)
  - Author: De La Ramee ("Ouida") Title: Granville de Vigne; or, held in bondage Series Title: Seaside Library Series Number: 981 City: New York Publisher: George Munro's Sons Date: 1886 (Box 21, Folder 429)
  - Author: De La Ramee ("Ouida") Title: In a winter city, a story of the day Series Title: Lippincott's Select Novels Series Number: 49 City: Philadelphia Publisher: J. B. Lippincott Date: 1886 (Box 21, Folder 430)
  - Author: De La Ramee ("Ouida") Title: Othmar Series Title: Lovell's Library Series Number: 790 City: New York Publisher: John W. Lovell Date: undated (Box 21, Folder 431)
  - Author: De La Ramee ("Ouida") Title: Pascarel, only a story Series Title: Seaside Library Series Number: 238 City: New York Publisher: George Munro's Sons Date: 1884 (Box 22, Folder 432)
  - Author: De La Ramee ("Ouida") Title: Princess Napraxine Series Title: Seaside Library Series Number: 228 City: New York Publisher: George Munro's Sons Date: 1884 (Box 22, Folder 433)
  - Author: De La Ramee ("Ouida") Title: Ruffino & c. Series Title: Seaside Library Series Number: 75 City: New York Publisher: George Munro Date: 1890 (Box 22, Folder 434)
  - Author: De La Ramee ("Ouida") Title: Santa Barbara Series Title: Lovell's International Series Series Number: 190 City: New York Publisher: John W. Lovell Date: 1891 (Box 22, Folder 435)
  - Author: De La Ramee ("Ouida") Title: Signa, a story Series Number: vol. VIII City: New York Publisher: P. F. Collier Format: hard cover Date: 1889 (Box 22, Folder 436)
  - Author: De La Ramee ("Ouida") Title: Folle-Farine Series Number: vol. VIII City: New York Publisher: P. F. Collier Format: hard cover Date: 1889 (Box 22, Folder 436)
  - Author: De La Ramee ("Ouida") Title: Sir Gallahad's raid Series Number: vol. VIII City: New York Publisher: P. F. Collier Format: hard cover Date: 1889 (Box 22, Folder 436)
  - Author: De La Ramee ("Ouida") Title: Strathmore; or, wrought by his own hand. A life romance Series Title: Seaside Library Series Number: 974 City: New York Publisher: George Munro Other Notes: first half Date: 1887 (Box 22, Folder 437)
  - Author: De La Ramee ("Ouida") Title: Strathmore; or, wrought by his own hand. A life romance Series Title: Seaside Library Series Number: 974 City: New York Publisher: George Munro Other Notes: second half Date: 1887 (Box 22, Folder 438)
  - Author: De La Ramee ("Ouida") Title: Syrlin or position Series Title: Seaside Library Series Number: 1308 City: New York Publisher: George Munro Date: 1890 (Box 22, Folder 439)
  - Author: De La Ramee ("Ouida") Title: Wanda, Countess Von Szalras Series Title: Seaside Library Series Number: 9 City: New York Publisher: George Munro Date: 1883 (Box 22, Folder 440)
  - Author: Delmar, Dora Title: For whose sake? Series Title: Library of American Authors Series Number: 78 City: New York Publisher: George Munro's Sons Date: 1893 (Box 22, Folder 441)
  - Author: Delmar, Dora Title: Half a truth Series Title: Modern Authors' Library Series Number: 573 City: Chicago Publisher: M. A. Donohue & Co Date: 1899 (Box 22, Folder 442)
  - Author: DeMille, James Title: The babes in the wood: a tragic comedy, a story of the Italian Revolution of 1848 City: Boston Publisher: William F. Gill & Company Format: hard cover Date: 1875 (Box 22, Folder 443)
  - Author: DeMille, James Title: The dodge club; or, Italy in MDCCCLIX City: New York Publisher: Harper & Brothers Format: hard cover Date: 1871 (Box 22, Folder 444)
  - Author: Denison, Mary A. Title: The daughter of the regiment Series Title: The Manhattan Series of Popular American Novels Series Number: 3 City: New York Publisher: A. L. Burt Date: 1888 (Box 22, Folder 445)
  - Author: Denison, Isabel Title: The discipline of life Series Title: Library of Select Novels Series Number: 119 City: New York Publisher: Harper & Brothers Date: 1848 (Box 22, Folder 446)
  - Author: Denison, Mary A. Title: A late repentance; or, the little white hand Series Title: Eagle Series Series Number: 310 City: New York Publisher: Street and Smith Date: 1889 (Box 22, Folder 447)
  - Author: D'Ennery Title: The two orphans Series Title: Munro's Library of Popular Novels Series Number: 56 City: New York Publisher: George Munro's Sons Other Notes: c. 1 Date: 1894 (Box 22, Folder 448)
  - Author: D'Ennery Title: The two orphans Series Title: Munro's Library of Popular Novels Series Number: 56 City: New York Publisher: George Munro's Sons Other Notes: c. 2 Date: 1894 (Box 23, Folder 449)
  - Author: De Pont-Jest, Rene Title: Artist and model (the divorced princess) Series Title: Hart Series Series Number: 171 City: Cleveland Publisher: Arthur Westbrook Date: undated (Box 23, Folder 450)
  - Title: Which shall it be? Format: hard cover Other Notes: bound together with Beneath the wheels, a romance; From Olympus to Hades; Fair Women; and Olive Varcoe or, true to the last Date: undated (Box 23, Folder 451)
  - Author: Derrick, Francis Title: Olive Varcoe or, true to the last Format: hard cover Other Notes: bound together with Beneath the wheels, a romance; From Olympus to Hades; Fair Women; and Which shall it be? Date: undated (Box 23, Folder 451)
  - Title: Fair Women Format: hard cover Other Notes: bound together with Beneath the wheels, a romance; From Olympus to Hades; Olive Varcoe or, true to the last; and Which shall it be? Date: undated (Box 23, Folder 451)
  - Title: From Olympus to Hades Format: hard cover Other Notes: bound together with Beneath the wheels, a romance; Olive Varcoe or, true to the last; Fair Women; and Which shall it be? Date: undated (Box 23, Folder 451)
  - Author: Derrick, Francis Title: Beneath the wheels, a romance City: New York Publisher: Harper & Brothers Format: hard cover Other Notes: bound together with Olive Varcoe or, true to the last; From Olympus to Hades; Fair Women; and Which shall it be? Date: 1870 (Box 23, Folder 451)
  - Author: De Trueba, Don T. Title: The incognito; or, sins and peccadilloes City: Philadelphia Publisher: Carey and Hart Format: hard cover Date: 1846 (Box 23, Folder 452)
  - Author: Douglas, Amanda Title: Lost in a great city Series Title: Good Company Series Series Number: 26 City: Boston Publisher: Lee and Shepard Date: 1893 (Box 23, Folder 453)
  - Author: Dowie, Muriel Menie Title: A girl in trousers, being the history of a young lady's adventures in the Karpathians Series Title: Leisure-Time Series Series Number: 9 City: New York Publisher: W. D. Rowland Date: 1891 (Box 23, Folder 454)
  - Author: Downey, Edmond Title: In one town Series Title: Munro's Library Series Number: vol. 50 no. 719 City: New York Publisher: Norman L. Munro Date: 1887 (Box 23, Folder 455)
  - Author: Doyle, A. Conan Title: Micah Clarke, his statement as given to his three grandchildren, Joseph, Gervas and Reuben, during the winter of 1734 Series Title: Arrow Library Series Number: 308 City: New York Publisher: Street and Smith Date: 1904 (Box 23, Folder 456)
  - Author: Du Boisgobey, F. Title: The coral pin Series Title: American Detective Series Series Number: 14 City: Cleveland Publisher: The Arthur Westbrook Company Date: 1883 (Box 23, Folder 457)
  - Author: Du Boisgobey, F. Title: Red lottery ticket Series Title: American Detective Series Series Number: 16 City: Cleveland Publisher: Arthur Westbrook Date: undated (Box 23, Folder 458)
  - Author: Du Boisgobey, F. Title: The temple of death, sequel to "The coral pin" Series Title: American Detective Series Series Number: 13 City: Cleveland Publisher: The Arthur Westbrook Company Date: 1899 (Box 23, Folder 459)
  - Author: Duchess, The Title: Airy fairy Lilian Series Title: Seaside Library Series Number: 14 City: New York Publisher: George Munro Date: 1883 (Box 23, Folder 460)
  - Author: Duchess, The Title: Airy fairy Lilian City: Chicago and New York Publisher: Belford, Clarke, & Co. Format: hard cover Date: undated (Box 23, Folder 461)
  - Author: Duchess, The Title: Airy fairy Lilian Series Title: Surprise Library Series Number: 14 City: New York Publisher: Surprise Library Date: undated (Box 23, Folder 462)
  - Author: Duchess, The Title: Airy fairy Lilian Series Title: Lovell's Library Series Number: 92 City: New York Publisher: John W. Lovell Date: 1883 (Box 23, Folder 463)
  - Author: Duchess, The Title: April's lady Series Title: Red Letter Series Series Number: 40 City: New York Publisher: The National Publishing Company Date: 1890 (Box 23, Folder 464)
  - Author: Duchess, The Title: April's lady, a novel of our own day Series Title: Aldis Series Series Number: 244 City: New York Publisher: F. M. Lupton Date: undated (Box 23, Folder 465)
  - Author: Duchess, The Title: April's lady, a novel of our own day City: New York Publisher: F. M. Lupton Format: hard cover Date: undated (Box 23, Folder 466)
  - Author: Duchess, The Title: The baby Series Title: The Victor Series of Paper Books Series Number: 224 City: New York Publisher: George Munro's Sons Other Notes: also contains One New Year's Eve and By death beleaguered by Percy Greg Date: undated (Box 23, Folder 467)
  - Author: Duchess, The Title: One New Year's Eve Series Title: The Victor Series of Paper Books Series Number: 224 City: New York Publisher: George Munro's Sons Other Notes: also contains One New Year's Eve and By death beleaguered by Percy Greg Date: undated (Box 23, Folder 467)
  - Author: Greg, Percy Title: By death beleaguered Series Title: The Victor Series of Paper Books Series Number: 224 City: New York Publisher: George Munro's Sons Other Notes: also contains One New Year's Eve by The Duchess and The baby by The Duchess Date: undated (Box 23, Folder 467)
  - Author: Duchess, The Title: Beauty's daughters; or, honest and true Series Title: Select Library Series Number: 93 City: New York Publisher: Street and Smith Date: undated (Box 24, Folder 468)
  - Author: Duchess, The Title: A born coquette Series Title: Once-A-Week Library Series Number: vol. 1, no. 23 City: New York Publisher: P. F. Collier Date: 1890 (Box 24, Folder 469)
  - Author: Duchess, The Title: Dick's sweetheart Series Title: Red Letter Series Series Number: 76 City: New York Publisher: International Book Company Date: 1895 (Box 24, Folder 470)
  - Author: Duchess, The Title: Doris, a love story Series Title: Surprise Library Series Number: 29 City: New York Publisher: Surprise Library Date: undated (Box 24, Folder 471)
  - Author: Duchess, The Title: The Duchess City: New York Publisher: F. M. Lupton Format: hard cover Date: undated (Box 24, Folder 472)
  - Author: Duchess, The Title: The Duchess Series Title: The Red Letter Series Series Number: 97 City: New York Publisher: National Publishing Co. Date: 1891 (Box 24, Folder 473)
  - Author: Duchess, The Title: The Duchess Series Title: The Bijou Series Series Number: 80 City: New York Publisher: F. M. Lupton Date: 1893 (Box 24, Folder 474)
  - Author: Duchess, The Title: The Duchess Series Title: Munro's Library of Popular Novels Series Number: 7 City: New York Publisher: George Munro's Sons Date: 1894 (Box 24, Folder 475)
  - Author: Duchess, The Title: The Duchess City: New York Publisher: George Munro's Sons Date: undated (Box 24, Folder 476)
  - Author: Duchess, The Title: The Duchess City: New York Publisher: F. M. Lupton Format: hard cover Date: undated (Box 24, Folder 477)
  - Author: Duchess, The Title: Faith and unfaith Series Title: Red Letter Series Series Number: 85 City: New York Publisher: International Book Company Date: 1895 (Box 24, Folder 478)
  - Author: Duchess, The Title: Faith and unfaith or, the torture of the jealous Series Title: Select Library Series Number: 165 City: New York Publisher: Street and Smith Date: undated (Box 24, Folder 479)
  - Author: Duchess, The Title: The haunted chamber Series Title: The Advance Library Series Number: 50 City: Springfield, MA Publisher: Springfield Publishing Co. Date: 1893 (Box 24, Folder 480)
  - Author: Duchess, The Title: The haunted chamber City: New York Publisher: The Mershon Company Format: hard cover Date: undated (Box 24, Folder 481)
  - Author: Duchess, The Title: Her last throw Series Title: The Savoy Series Series Number: 31 City: New York Publisher: George Munro's Sons Date: undated (Box 24, Folder 482)
  - Author: Duchess, The Title: Her last throw Series Title: Lovell's Modern Novelists' Series Series Number: 6 City: New York Publisher: Home Book Company Date: 1893 (Box 24, Folder 483)
  - Author: Duchess, The Title: The honourable Mrs. Vereker Series Title: Arrow Library Series Number: 62 City: New York Publisher: Street and Smith Date: 1898 (Box 24, Folder 484)
  - Author: Duchess, The Title: The honourable Mrs. Vereker Series Title: Select Library Series Number: 146 City: New York Publisher: Street and Smith Date: undated (Box 24, Folder 485)
  - Author: Duchess, The Title: The hoyden Series Title: Lippincott's Select Novels Series Number: 147 City: Philadelphia Publisher: J. B. Lippincott Date: 1893 (Box 24, Folder 486)
  - Author: Duchess, The Title: Moonshine and marguerites Series Title: Lippincott's Select Novels Series Number: 33 City: Philadelphia Publisher: J. B. Lippincott Other Notes: also contains A week in Killarney, In Durance Vile, Dr. Ball, A fit of the blues Date: 1886 (Box 24, Folder 487)
  - Author: Duchess, The Title: In Durance Vile, and other stories Series Title: Lippincott's Select Novels Series Number: 33 City: Philadelphia Publisher: J. B. Lippincott Other Notes: also contains A week in Killarney, Moonshine and marguerites, Dr. Ball, A fit of the blues Date: 1886 (Box 24, Folder 487)
  - Author: Duchess, The Title: A fit of the blues Series Title: Lippincott's Select Novels Series Number: 33 City: Philadelphia Publisher: J. B. Lippincott Other Notes: also contains A week in Killarney, Moonshine and marguerites, Dr. Ball, In Durance Vile Date: 1886 (Box 24, Folder 487)
  - Author: Duchess, The Title: Dr. Ball Series Title: Lippincott's Select Novels Series Number: 33 City: Philadelphia Publisher: J. B. Lippincott Other Notes: also contains A week in Killarney, Moonshine and marguerites, In Durance Vile, A fit of the blues Date: 1886 (Box 24, Folder 487)
  - Author: Duchess, The Title: A week in Killarney Series Title: Lippincott's Select Novels Series Number: 33 City: Philadelphia Publisher: J. B. Lippincott Other Notes: also contains In Durance Vile, Moonshine and marguerites, Dr. Ball, A fit of the blues Date: 1886 (Box 24, Folder 487)
  - Author: Duchess, The Title: In Durance Vile Series Title: The Arm Chair Library Series Number: 44 City: New York Publisher: F. M. Lupton Date: 1893 (Box 24, Folder 489)
  - Author: Duchess, The Title: Lady Branksmere City: New York Publisher: F. M. Lupton Format: hard cover Date: undated (Box 25, Folder 490)
  - Author: Duchess, The Title: Lady Branksmere City: Chicago Publisher: Donohue, Henneberry, & Co. Format: hard cover Date: undated (Box 25, Folder 491)
  - Author: Duchess, The Title: Lady Branksmere Series Title: The Ideal Library Series Number: 180 City: Chicago Publisher: Donohue, Henneberry, & Co. Date: 1895 (Box 25, Folder 492)
  - Author: Duchess, The Title: Lady Valworth's diamonds Series Title: Sunset Series Series Number: 172 City: New York Publisher: J. S. Ogilvie Date: undated (Box 25, Folder 493)
  - Author: Duchess, The Title: A life's remorse Series Title: Seaside Library Series Number: 1249 City: New York Publisher: George Munro Date: 1889 (Box 25, Folder 494)
  - Author: Duchess, The Title: A little Irish girl Series Title: Munro's Library of Popular Novels Series Number: 45 City: New York Publisher: George Munro's Sons Date: 1894 (Box 25, Folder 495)
  - Author: Duchess, The Title: A little rebel Series Title: The Bijou Series Series Number: 7 City: New York Publisher: F. M. Lupton Date: 1892 (Box 25, Folder 496)
  - Author: Duchess, The Title: A little rebel Series Title: The Surprise Series Series Number: 153 City: New York Publisher: International Book Company Date: 1891 (Box 25, Folder 497)
  - Author: Duchess, The Title: Lovice Series Title: Lippincott's Select Novels Series Number: 232 City: Philadelphia Publisher: J. B. Lippincott Date: 1900 (Box 25, Folder 498)
  - Author: Duchess, The Title: Loys, Lord Berresford Series Title: The Seaside Library Series Number: 118 City: New York Publisher: George Munro Date: 1883 (Box 25, Folder 499)
  - Author: Duchess, The Title: Eric Dering Series Title: The Seaside Library Series Number: 118 City: New York Publisher: George Munro Date: 1883 (Box 25, Folder 499)
  - Author: Duchess, The Title: Loys, Lord Berresford Series Title: Seaside Library Series Number: 135 City: New York Publisher: George Munro Date: 1887 (Box 25, Folder 500)
  - Author: Duchess, The Title: A maiden all forlorn Series Title: Atlantic Library Series Number: 35 Date: undated (Box 25, Folder 501)
  - Author: Duchess, The Title: Marvel Series Title: Seaside Library Series Number: 169 City: New York Publisher: George Munro Date: 1888 (Box 25, Folder 502)
  - Author: Duchess, The Title: Marvel City: New York Publisher: F. M. Lupton Format: hard cover Date: undated (Box 25, Folder 503)
  - Author: Duchess, The Title: Marvel Series Title: Lippincott's Select Novels Series Number: 82 City: Philadelphia Publisher: J. B. Lippincott Date: 1888 (Box 25, Folder 504)
  - Author: Duchess, The Title: A mental struggle Series Title: Sunset Series Series Number: 178 City: New York Publisher: J. S. Ogilvie Date: undated (Box 25, Folder 505)
  - Author: Duchess, The Title: Mildred Trevanion City: Chicago Publisher: Fred C. Laird Format: hard cover Date: undated (Box 25, Folder 506)
  - Author: Duchess, The Title: A modern circe Series Title: Seaside Library Series Number: 164 City: New York Publisher: George Munro Date: 1887 (Box 25, Folder 507)
  - Author: Duchess, The Title: A modern circe Series Title: Select Library Series Number: 134 City: New York Publisher: Street and Smith Date: undated (Box 25, Folder 508)
  - Author: Duchess, The Title: A modern circe City: New York Publisher: F. M. Lupton Format: hard cover Date: undated (Box 25, Folder 509)
  - Author: Duchess, The Title: Molly Bawn Series Title: Chelsea Series Series Number: 106 City: New York Publisher: American Publishers Corporation Date: undated (Box 26, Folder 510)
  - Author: Duchess, The Title: Molly Bawn Series Title: Seaside Library Series Number: 2 City: New York Publisher: George Munro Date: 1887 (Box 26, Folder 511)
  - Author: Duchess, The Title: Moonshine and marguerites Series Title: Munro's Library of Popular Novels Series Number: 95 City: New York Publisher: George Munro's Sons Date: 1894 (Box 26, Folder 512)
  - Author: Duchess, The Title: Mrs. Geoffrey Series Title: Select Library Series Number: 127 City: New York Publisher: Street and Smith Other Notes: missing the first few pages Date: undated (Box 26, Folder 513)
  - Author: Duchess, The Title: Nurse Eva Series Title: The Handy Classic Series Series Number: 20 City: New York Publisher: Optimus Printing Company Date: undated (Box 26, Folder 514)
  - Author: Duchess, The Title: Nurse Eva Series Title: Neely's Booklets City: New York Publisher: F. Tennyson Neely Date: 1899 (Box 26, Folder 515)
  - Author: Duchess, The Title: A passive crime Series Title: The Advance Library Series Number: 64 City: Springfield, MA Publisher: Springfield Publishing Co. Date: 1893 (Box 26, Folder 516)
  - Author: Duchess, The Title: Portia; or, "by passions rocked" Series Title: The Seaside Library Series Number: 124 City: New York Publisher: George Munro's Sons Date: 1896 (Box 26, Folder 517)
  - Author: Duchess, The Title: Portia City: New York Publisher: Hurst and Company Format: hard cover Date: undated (Box 26, Folder 518)
  - Author: Duchess, The Title: Portia; or, by passions rocked Series Title: The Chimney Corner Series Series Number: 72 City: New York Publisher: F. M. Lupton Format: hard cover Date: undated (Box 26, Folder 519)
  - Author: Hungerford, Mrs. (The Duchess) Title: The professor's experiment Series Title: Fenno's Select Series Series Number: 13 City: New York Publisher: R. F. Fenno & Company Date: 1895 (Box 26, Folder 520)
  - Author: Duchess, The Title: Sweet is true love Series Title: Munro's Library of Popular Novels Series Number: 55 City: New York Publisher: George Munro's Sons Date: 1894 (Box 26, Folder 521)
  - Author: Duchess, The Title: A troublesome girl Series Title: The Advance Library Series Number: 77 City: Springfield, MA Publisher: Springfield Publishing Co. Date: 1893 (Box 26, Folder 522)
  - Author: Duchess, The Title: A troublesome girl Series Title: The Bijou Series Series Number: 85 City: New York Publisher: F. M. Lupton Date: 1893 (Box 26, Folder 523)
  - Author: Duchess, The Title: Under-currents Series Title: Select Library Series Number: 84 City: New York Publisher: Street and Smith Date: undated (Box 26, Folder 524)
  - Author: Duchess, The Title: Under-currents Series Title: Hart Series Series Number: 124 City: Cleveland Publisher: Arthur Westbrook Date: undated (Box 26, Folder 525)
  - Author: Duchess, The Title: A week in Killarney Series Title: Munro's Library of Popular Novels Series Number: 215 City: New York Publisher: George Munro's Sons Date: 1896 (Box 26, Folder 526)
  - Author: Duchess, The Title: The witching hour, and other stories Series Title: Munro's Library of Popular Novels Series Number: 79 City: New York Publisher: George Munro's Sons Date: 1896 (Box 26, Folder 527)